Tufts University Television (TUTV) Records UA076
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiovisual materials, UA076.002
  - Tape 221, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Tape 18, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Tape 36 taping of rehearsals Spirit of Color, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Tape 217 tufts distinguished achievement awards, 1999; UA076.002.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Tape 219, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Tape 191 The Legacy act I, act II, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Tape 216, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Tape 60, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Tape 198 Bowl Haven, 1999-02-23; UA076.002.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Tape 220 TUTV retrospectives, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Tape 54 exp 58a, 1995-06; UA076.002.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Tape 35 S71, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Tape 26, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Tape 45 the street buzz, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Tape 42, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Tape 185 JMP's feature 'Skin', 1999-04-20; UA076.002.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Tape 41 MF final exam ASL, 1994-08-10 -- 1994-08-11; UA076.002.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Tape 46 Tufts Tomorrow, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Tape 43, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Tape 53 "Rebel" exp 58a, 1995-06; UA076.002.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Tape 51, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Tape 224 supershow 2, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Tape 223 supershow 1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - OCL intro, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Tape 199 HEI morning poster session, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Tape 197 sports doc Jon Black's farewell, 2000-03-31; UA076.002.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Tape 213 the show, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Tape 205, 1999-11-04; UA076.002.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Tape 218, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Tape 200 on campus live 501, 1999-10-14; UA076.002.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Tape 193 studio shoot, 1999-11-14; UA076.002.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Tape 194 TUTV editing, 1995-11-08; UA076.002.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Tape 87 Tufts sailing, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Tape 141 video class, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Tape 122 master tape women's crew, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Tape 34, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Tape 28 David lecture, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Tape 40 blind date, 1981-10-22; UA076.002.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Tape 21 music video parts, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Tape 11, 1979-03-29; UA076.002.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - 1 TUTV demo, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Tape 29 practice tape for Apple Jam Video Productions, 1979-12; UA076.002.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Tape 22 slides and "Better Believe" takes, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Tape 26 Blind Date, 1978-11-30; UA076.002.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Tape 20 The Roommate Game, 1981-03-05; UA076.002.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Tape 27 Trivia Triangle, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Untitled, circa 1960 -- 1970s; UA076.002.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Tape 23 Rolling Stones and Hampton Court, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Tape 6 spy pond freestyle, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Tape 5 sailing team footage, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Tape 131 final cut Big Bird, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Tape 132 on campus 303, 1998-12-02; UA076.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Tape 133 ivory tower combat 3, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Tape 168 Gen X, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Tape 106 Macbeth, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Tape 80, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Tape 105 playtape, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Tape 79, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Tape 81, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Tape 78 Five Female Persuasions Peter Hixson, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Tape 108, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Tape 107, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Tape 65 on the hill, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Tape 58 Fantastic Voyage, 1995-02; UA076.002.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Tape 72, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Tape 71, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Tape 98 dark corners "Turnabout", circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Tape 61, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Tape 62 ivory tower combat, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Tape 63 ivory tower combat, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Tape 64, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Tape 77, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Tape 76, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Tape 66, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Tape 70, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - Tape 136, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Tape 135, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Tape 69, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Tape 57 forum, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Tape 137 SCAT rool in package, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - Tape 93, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Tape 113, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - Tape 171 "On Campus" episode 1, 1997; UA076.002.016.00036 (Box 16)
  - Tape 114 MLK footage, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00037 (Box 16)
  - Tape 104, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00038 (Box 16)
  - Accompanying materials for UA076.002.016.00013, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.016.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16)
  - Tape 14, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
    Dates of materials in box 17 reflect the date materials were logged by TUTV, not necessarily the date events took place.
  - Tape 13, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Tape 11, 1999-12-01; UA076.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Tape 179 candid camera prank 1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Tape 1 the leadership experience, 1999-10-08; UA076.002.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Tape 15, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Tape 181 perspective 101, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Tape 30, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Tape 5, 1999-10-21; UA076.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Tape 7, 1999-11-22; UA076.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Tape 2, 1999-10-20; UA076.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Tape 31 s65, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Tape 3, 1999-10-20; UA076.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Tape 4, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Tape 8, 1999-10-20; UA076.002.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Tape 9, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Tape 16, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - HOC Courier, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Tape 10, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Tape 170 on campus episode 200, 1997 -- 1998; UA076.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Tape 172 on campus 302, 1998 -- 1999; UA076.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Tape 118, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Tape 119, 1998-11-03; UA076.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Tape 120, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Tape 85 the leadership experience, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Tape 178 "Candid Camera", circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Tape 175, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Tape 180, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Tape 176, 1999-04-28; UA076.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Tape 177, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Tape 182 Tufts men's bball, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Tape 183, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Tape 165 Woonsocket 102, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Tape 174 on campus 401, 1999-03-06; UA076.002.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - Tape 173 on campus 202, 1998-04-08; UA076.002.017.00035 (Box 17)
  - Tape 166 higher education initiatives, 1997 -- 1998; UA076.002.017.00036 (Box 17)
  - Tape 86 I'm different, you're different, we're both okay, 1988-08-31; UA076.002.017.00037 (Box 17)
  - Tape 12, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00038 (Box 17)
  - Tape 117 broadcast tape 1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.017.00039 (Box 17)
  - Tape 115 almost ivy 201, 1998 -- 1999; UA076.002.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Tape 103 diversity panel discussion, 1988-11-14; UA076.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Tape 101 Taming of the Shrew, 1996-04; UA076.002.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Tape 116 Almost Ivy 101, 102, 1997 -- 1998; UA076.002.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Tape 112 screen tests, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Tape 150 final cut Salem state, 1997 -- 1998; UA076.002.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Tape 102 drumming, 1998-09-25 -- 1998-10-01; UA076.002.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Tape 95, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - 14 TUTV headers and commercials, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - 16 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Tape 191 sportsdoc 101, 1998 -- 1999; UA076.002.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Tape 56, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Tape 210 OCL promo, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Tape 209 OCL, 2000-04-03; UA076.002.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Tape 195 boys soccer and homecoming, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Tape 202 OCL, 1999-12-09; UA076.002.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Tape 201 OCL, 1999-12-09; UA076.002.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Tape 212 life in the day, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Tape 211 casting couch, 2000-04-03; UA076.002.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Tape 192 sports doc studio taping show 101, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Tape 196 TUTV on SCAT, 1999-03-03; UA076.002.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Tape 207 on campus live, 2000-03-06; UA076.002.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Tape 206 OCL, 2000-02-17; UA076.002.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Tape 55, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Tape 37, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Tape 187 program tape, 1998-12-08; UA076.002.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Tape 34 s70, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Tape 32, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Tape 17, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Tape 33, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Tape 208, 2000-03-06; UA076.002.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Tape 204 taping of live show behind the scenes, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Tape 215 newsmag episode 101, 1999-10-21; UA076.002.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Tape 214, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Tape 49 opening up the classroom, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Tape 47 beyond Big Bird, 1997-04-07; UA076.002.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Tape 59 program tape, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Tape 203 program block tape 1 OCL, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Tape 188 Dinchel and Cooter episode 1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Tape 189, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Tape 190 vice president studio HEI, 1998-04-22; UA076.002.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Tape 39, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Tape 222 glasswang open, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - Tape 38, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Tape 22, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - Tape 186 program tape version 2, 1998-03-10; UA076.002.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - Tape 52, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - Tape 50 Shakespeare raw, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.018.00048 (Box 19)
  - Multimedia day Olin Center, 1998-03-10; UA076.002.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Somerville Rotary spring gala, 1999; UA076.002.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - New England Medical Center, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Somerville Rotary PSA, 1998-01; UA076.002.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Ep 11c channel 5 and 7, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - PSA Somerville unites for human rights conference, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Tape 5 British TV, the war game, and threads, 1965 -- 1985; UA076.002.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Introduction to the theory of public international law Prof. Alfred P. Rubing, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Teleconference graduate advertising, 1993-10-28; UA076.002.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Tape 6 British TV, the Atomic Café, Reservations, 1985-08 -- 1985-09; UA076.002.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Samurai delicatessen John Belushi, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Tufts television archive UK, 1985-02-24; UA076.002.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - The Jazz Singer, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - The tradition of the Olympic games on television, 1996-04-22; UA076.002.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Trans world sport Bud Greespan excerpt, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Trans world sport Bud Greespan excerpt, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Ball State for ED, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - OCLC videoconference the electronic library, 1994-10-01; UA076.002.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Kennedy School Christmas rap Somerville, 1989-12-21; UA076.002.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - The tradition of sportscasting, 1996-04-23; UA076.002.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - IAT libraries today's issues, tomorrow's challenges, 1994-12-01; UA076.002.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Teleconference sexual harassment, 1992-11-12; UA076.002.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Teleconference: Black issues in higher education, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - ACTFL teleconference national standards in foreign language education, 1994-11-18; UA076.002.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Women negotiate, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Prof Vida Johnson Christian Science Monitor cranes are flying interview, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Charley Rose interview with Jean Mayer The Learning Channel, 1992-06-10; UA076.002.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Testing and assessment in the second language classroom McGraw Hill, 2004-10-27; UA076.002.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - AV services committee visit to Brandeis, visit to BC, 1988-06-13 -- 1988-06-30; UA076.002.019.00029 (Box 19)